

Profile

Motivated Graphic Designer & Video Editor with 7 years of hands-on experience in the management of the complete design process, from conceptualization to delivery. Expert at interdepartmental coordination, team lead and communication. Skilled with Adobe Creative Suite (Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign, After effects and Premiere pro for editing videos), and Web design applications (Dreamweaver, HTML). Able to stretch the boundaries of web design to help my client's brands stand out.

Contact

- **(a)** +91 9700 4511 37
- tushartiwari444@gmail.com
- Boduppal, Hyderabad-500092.
- www.behance.net/tushartiwari

Skills

Graphic Design



Motion Design Web Design



Language







HINDI



Passion









TUSHAR TIWARI

Graphic Designer & Video Editor

Work Experience



Apr 2021-Till Date

Graphic Designer & Video Editor DigiMasters India Pvt. Ltd.

A platform for e-learning, creating video's for students according to the subjects.

Oct 2020-Apr 2021

Graphic Desinger & Video Editor

Robotouch (Bhagya Laxmi Industries) & HerbHair.

Worked on Image editing, Standee for promotions, Branding, Website cover pages, Website landing pages, Video editing, and Herbhair social media posts.

Mar 2020-Sep 2020

Graphic Desinger

Affinity Express India Pvt. Ltd. (Pune)

Worked on image editing, and graphics for promotions, print and decorated apparel.

Nov 2019-Feb 2020

Image Editor

TULFA Private Limited

Worked on E-commerce companies products Image Editing

Jul 2016-Oct 2019

Graphic Designer & Video Editor

Sai Learners Valley Education Private Ltd.

· Worked on Social Media Post for Banners, Posters, Flyers and Brochure designs and Video's Editing subject related, Timelines, Infographics, and Website cover page.

EDUCATION



B.COM(COMP) Intermediate(MPC) SSC